{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/449","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"449","name":"Clique Restaurant","address":"1326 Jefferson Ave. E.","zipcode":"48207","owner":"Marina Dokic","licenseNumber":"034231","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"150","coords":"-83.03353,42.33320","geojson":{"id":"449","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.03353118,42.33319854]},"properties":{"name":"Clique Restaurant","owner":"Marina Dokic","address":"1326 Jefferson Ave. E.","zipcode":"48207","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"034231","establishmentid":"449","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"150","most_recent_license_date":"2022-05-09"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"774","name":"Disabled American Veterans","address":"1360 Jefferson E.","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"2688","name":"Filterfresh","address":"1000 Woodbridge","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"4450","name":"Happy's Pizza #99","address":"1404 Jefferson Ave E.","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"2623","name":"Alabama Style Chicken & Fish","address":"1404 Jefferson Ave. E.","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"775","name":"Yondotega Club","address":"1450 Jefferson Ave. E.","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"3663","name":"Vondie's On the River","address":"260 Schweizer Place","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"2164","name":"Captain's Bar & Grill","address":"260 Schweizer Place","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"2357","name":"Steve's Soul Food Det/The Key Club","address":"1440 Franklin","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"51623685","name":"The Breakfast Loft Inc ","address":"1440 Franklin St Suit 300","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"51623274","name":"Steve's World of Food--FOOD TRUCK","address":"1440 Franklin","zipcode":"48207"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"62060","inspectionDate":"2023-04-03T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"On the Cookline","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2023-04-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not meet requirements of rule","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Dishwasher","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the Grill","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"On the Cookline","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2023-04-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"59843","inspectionDate":"2022-07-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\n\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Chlorine solution concentration","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 25 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Dishwasher (low temperature)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-07-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"On the Counter(s)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-07-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.13","violationDescription":"POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be thawed:  Under refrigeration, or under cool running water (<70° F), or as part of cooking process, and total accumulated time above 41° F, for thawed portions, shall not exceed 4 hours.  Any thawing procedure may be used for immediate service for individual consumers order of READY-TO-EAT foods.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Frozen food(s) for thawing","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F thawed or partially thawed","subProblem":"At room temperature","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"On the Counter(s)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2022-07-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"On the Ceiling (s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"57168","inspectionDate":"2022-02-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\n\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Chlorine solution concentration","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 25 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Dishwasher (low temperature)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-02-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."},{"violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"On the Ceiling (s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"54900","inspectionDate":"2021-05-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-202.12","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS shall be:    \n(A) Used according to:      \n(1) LAW and this Code,   \n(2) Manufacturer's use directions included in labeling, and, for a pesticide, manufacturer's label instructions that state that use is allowed in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, (P)   \n(3) The conditions of certification, if certification is required, for use of the pest control materials, (P) and   \n(4) Additional conditions that may be established by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY; and\n(B) Applied so that:      \n(1) A HAZARD to EMPLOYEES or other PERSONS is not constituted, (P) and   \n(2) Contamination including toxic residues due to drip, drain, fog, splash or spray on FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES is prevented, and for a RESTRICTED USE PESTICIDE, this is achieved by: (P)      \n(a) Removing the items, (P)   \n(b) Covering the items with impermeable covers, (P) or   \n(c) Taking other appropriate preventive actions, (P) and   \n(d) Cleaning and SANITIZING EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS after the application. (P)  \n(C) A RESTRICTED USE PESTICIDE shall be applied only by an applicator certified as defined in 7 USC 136 Definitions, (e) Certified Applicator, of the Federal Insecticide, Fungicide, and Rodenticide Act, or a PERSON under the direct supervision of a certified applicator. (Pf)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not used according to manufacturer's label instructions","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"On the wall","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-05-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"On the Ceiling (s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the Grill","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2021-05-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."}]},{"inspectionid":"52716","inspectionDate":"2020-09-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"In the Reach-in cooler","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-09-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\n\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Chlorine solution concentration","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 25 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Dishwasher (low temperature)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-09-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"BACK PREPARATION AREA","subLocation":"At the Ceiling (s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the Grill","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2020-09-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING/PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Cooler(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"52548","inspectionDate":"2020-07-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"50744","inspectionDate":"2020-02-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"In the Reach-in cooler","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-02-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-301.14","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall clean their hands and exposed portions of their arms as specified under § 2-301.12 immediately before engaging in FOOD preparation including working with exposed FOOD, clean EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES (P) and:\n(A)     After touching bare human body parts other than clean hands and clean, exposed portions of arms; (P)\n(B)     After using the toilet room; (P)\n(C)     After caring for or handling SERVICE ANIMALS or aquatic animals as specified in ¶ 2-403.11(B); (P).\n(D)     Except as specified in ¶ 2-401.11(B), after coughing, sneezing, using a handkerchief or disposable tissue, using tobacco, eating, or drinking; (P)\n(E)     After handling soiled EQUIPMENT or UTENSILS; (P)\n(F)     During FOOD preparation, as often as necessary to remove soil and contamination and to prevent cross contamination when changing tasks; (P)\n(G)     When switching between working with raw FOOD and working with READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\n(H)     Before donning gloves for working with FOOD; (P) and\n(I)      After engaging in other activities that contaminate the hands. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Did not wash hands","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"On the Cookline","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-02-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\n\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Chlorine solution concentration","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 25 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Dishwasher (low temperature)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-02-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING/PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Cooler(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the Grill","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"BACK PREPARATION AREA","subLocation":"Under the Equipment","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"48702","inspectionDate":"2019-08-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-08-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.15","violationDescription":"(A) SINGLE-USE gloves shall be used for one task only and discarded when      damaged, soiled, or when interruptions occur in the operation. (P)\n\n(B) Slash-resistant and cloth gloves shall be used in direct contact only with FOOD that is subsequently cooked. Gloves used with ready-to-eat foods shall be smooth,   durable and non-absorbant.\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Single-use glove(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for multiple purposes","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-08-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Gloves shall only be used for one purpose and then disposed."},{"violationCode":"3-501.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cooked POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be cooled:\n         (1)  Within 2 hours, from 135ºF to 70ºF; and (P) \n         (2)  Within 4 hours, from 70ºF to 41ºF or less (P)\n(B)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared from ingredients at ambient temperature shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41F or less. (P)\n(C)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  received in compliance with LAWS   allowing a temperature above 41ºF during shipment from the supplier shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41ºF or less. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cooked food(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"From 135 degrees f to 70 degrees F for more than 2 hours","subProblem":"","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-08-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Utilize shallow pans, ice baths, agitation, or quick chilling to cool food items."},{"violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-08-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-502.11","violationDescription":"(A) UTENSILS shall be maintained in a state of repair or condition that complies with the requirements specified under Parts 4-1 and 4-2 or shall be discarded.\n(B) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be calibrated in accordance with manufacturer's specifications as necessary to ensure their accuracy. (Pf)   \n(C) Ambient air temperature, water pressure, and water TEMPERATURE MEAURING DEVICES shall be maintained in good repair and be accurate within the intended range of use.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not calibrated","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"with the Thermometer(s)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-08-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"In the Back Room","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to prevent pest entry","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"At the Back door","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"45183","inspectionDate":"2019-02-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-02-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"3-304.15","violationDescription":"(A) SINGLE-USE gloves shall be used for one task only and discarded when      damaged, soiled, or when interruptions occur in the operation. (P)\n\n(B) Slash-resistant and cloth gloves shall be used in direct contact only with FOOD that is subsequently cooked. Gloves used with ready-to-eat foods shall be smooth,   durable and non-absorbant.\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Single-use glove(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for multiple purposes","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-02-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Gloves shall only be used for one purpose and then disposed."},{"violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"Covered","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"In the Cooler(meat)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-02-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Cool items uncovered on the top shelf of cooler."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Utensil(s) knives","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"In the Knife rack","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-02-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"3-304.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cloths that are in use for wiping FOOD spills on TABLEWARE shall be maintained dry and used for no other purpose. \n(B)  Cloths in-use for wiping counters and equipment shall be held between uses in   a chemical sanitizer solution, and laundered daily.\n(C)  Cloths in-use for wiping surfaces in contact with raw animal FOODS shall be      kept separate from cloths used for other purposes.\n(D)  Dry wiping cloths and the chemical sanitizing solutions shall be free of FOOD    debris or visible soil.\n(E)  Containers of chemical sanitizing solutions shall be stored off the floor and         used in a manner that prevents contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, SINGLE-SERVICE, or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n(E)  SINGLE-USE disposable sanitizer wipes shall be used in accordance lable               instructions.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wiping cloth(s)","subItem":"wet","problemDescription":"Stored on","subProblem":"Counter","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"and the Prep area","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-02-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store wiping cloths completely submersed in sanitizer."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"EQUIPMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/Replace"}]},{"inspectionid":"45184","inspectionDate":"2018-07-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not approved for use","subProblem":"","location":"SANITIZER BUCKETS","subLocation":"At the Sanitizer","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discontinue use."},{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) and utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"At least every 4 hours during continual use","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"On the Counter(s)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean as specified above."},{"violationCode":"3-501.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cooked POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be cooled:\n         (1)  Within 2 hours, from 135ºF to 70ºF; and (P) \n         (2)  Within 4 hours, from 70ºF to 41ºF or less (P)\n(B)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared from ingredients at ambient temperature shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41F or less. (P)\n(C)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  received in compliance with LAWS   allowing a temperature above 41ºF during shipment from the supplier shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41ºF or less. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cooked food(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"From 70 degrees f to 41 degrees F for more than 4 hours","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"In the Cooler(meat)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the COLD HOLDING TEMPERATURES","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"Covered","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"In the Cooler(meat)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Cool items uncovered on the top shelf of cooler."},{"violationCode":"6-404.11","violationDescription":"Products that are held by the PERMIT HOLDER for credit, redemption, or return to the distributor, such as damaged, spoiled, or recalled products, shall be segregated and held in designated areas that are separated from FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Distressed merchandise for return/credit","subItem":"damaged","problemDescription":"Not separated from","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA(S)","subLocation":"On the Shelves","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate separation to prevent contamination."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Equipment can openers","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"In the Back Room","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"EQUIPMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/Replace"},{"violationCode":"3-304.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cloths that are in use for wiping FOOD spills on TABLEWARE shall be maintained dry and used for no other purpose. \n(B)  Cloths in-use for wiping counters and equipment shall be held between uses in   a chemical sanitizer solution, and laundered daily.\n(C)  Cloths in-use for wiping surfaces in contact with raw animal FOODS shall be      kept separate from cloths used for other purposes.\n(D)  Dry wiping cloths and the chemical sanitizing solutions shall be free of FOOD    debris or visible soil.\n(E)  Containers of chemical sanitizing solutions shall be stored off the floor and         used in a manner that prevents contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, SINGLE-SERVICE, or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n(E)  SINGLE-USE disposable sanitizer wipes shall be used in accordance lable               instructions.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wiping cloth(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored in","subProblem":"Less than 50-100 ppm chlorine","location":"WIPING CLOTHS","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-07-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store wiping cloths in 50-100 ppm chlorine."}]},{"inspectionid":"39899","inspectionDate":"2017-09-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\n\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-10-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall only contact surfaces of EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS that are cleaned and SANITIZED, or SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not properly cleaned and sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-10-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Equipment shall be washed, rinsed, and sanitized after contamination and between uses."},{"violationCode":"2-301.14","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall clean their hands and exposed portions of their arms as specified under § 2-301.12 immediately before engaging in FOOD preparation including working with exposed FOOD, clean EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES (P) and:\n(A)     After touching bare human body parts other than clean hands and clean, exposed portions of arms; (P)\n(B)     After using the toilet room; (P)\n(C)     After caring for or handling SERVICE ANIMALS or aquatic animals as specified in ¶ 2-403.11(B); (P).\n(D)     Except as specified in ¶ 2-401.11(B), after coughing, sneezing, using a handkerchief or disposable tissue, using tobacco, eating, or drinking; (P)\n(E)     After handling soiled EQUIPMENT or UTENSILS; (P)\n(F)     During FOOD preparation, as often as necessary to remove soil and contamination and to prevent cross contamination when changing tasks; (P)\n(G)     When switching between working with raw FOOD and working with READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\n(H)     Before donning gloves for working with FOOD; (P) and\n(I)      After engaging in other activities that contaminate the hands. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Did not wash hands","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Hands shall be washed with hot water and soap for at least 20 seconds after contamination."},{"violationCode":"3-501.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cooked POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be cooled:\n         (1)  Within 2 hours, from 135ºF to 70ºF; and (P) \n         (2)  Within 4 hours, from 70ºF to 41ºF or less (P)\n(B)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared from ingredients at ambient temperature shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41F or less. (P)\n(C)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  received in compliance with LAWS   allowing a temperature above 41ºF during shipment from the supplier shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41ºF or less. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cooked food(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"From 135 degrees f to 70 degrees F for more than 2 hours","subProblem":"","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Utilize shallow pans, ice baths, agitation, or quick chilling to cool food items."},{"violationCode":"3-304.15","violationDescription":"(A) SINGLE-USE gloves shall be used for one task only and discarded when      damaged, soiled, or when interruptions occur in the operation. (P)\n\n(B) Slash-resistant and cloth gloves shall be used in direct contact only with FOOD that is subsequently cooked. Gloves used with ready-to-eat foods shall be smooth,   durable and non-absorbant.\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Single-use glove(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for multiple purposes","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Gloves shall only be used for one purpose and then disposed."},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-10-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-103.11","violationDescription":"The PERSON IN CHARGE shall ensure that employees, practices and policies are in compliance with the code. (Pf) \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not ensuring compliance","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Person-in-charge must ensure compliance with items listed above."},{"violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-10-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"violationCode":"3-304.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cloths that are in use for wiping FOOD spills on TABLEWARE shall be maintained dry and used for no other purpose. \n(B)  Cloths in-use for wiping counters and equipment shall be held between uses in   a chemical sanitizer solution, and laundered daily.\n(C)  Cloths in-use for wiping surfaces in contact with raw animal FOODS shall be      kept separate from cloths used for other purposes.\n(D)  Dry wiping cloths and the chemical sanitizing solutions shall be free of FOOD    debris or visible soil.\n(E)  Containers of chemical sanitizing solutions shall be stored off the floor and         used in a manner that prevents contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, SINGLE-SERVICE, or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n(E)  SINGLE-USE disposable sanitizer wipes shall be used in accordance lable               instructions.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wiping cloth(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored in","subProblem":"Less than 50-100 ppm chlorine","location":"WIPING CLOTHS","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store wiping cloths in 50-100 ppm chlorine."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not meet requirements of rule","subProblem":"","location":"FREEZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements of rule."},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"59873","inspectionDate":"2017-07-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"3-501.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cooked POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be cooled:\n         (1)  Within 2 hours, from 135ºF to 70ºF; and (P) \n         (2)  Within 4 hours, from 70ºF to 41ºF or less (P)\n(B)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared from ingredients at ambient temperature shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41F or less. (P)\n(C)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  received in compliance with LAWS   allowing a temperature above 41ºF during shipment from the supplier shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41ºF or less. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cooked food(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"From 135 degrees f to 70 degrees F for more than 2 hours","subProblem":"","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Utilize shallow pans, ice baths, agitation, or quick chilling to cool food items."},{"violationCode":"2-301.14","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall clean their hands and exposed portions of their arms as specified under § 2-301.12 immediately before engaging in FOOD preparation including working with exposed FOOD, clean EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES (P) and:\n(A)     After touching bare human body parts other than clean hands and clean, exposed portions of arms; (P)\n(B)     After using the toilet room; (P)\n(C)     After caring for or handling SERVICE ANIMALS or aquatic animals as specified in ¶ 2-403.11(B); (P).\n(D)     Except as specified in ¶ 2-401.11(B), after coughing, sneezing, using a handkerchief or disposable tissue, using tobacco, eating, or drinking; (P)\n(E)     After handling soiled EQUIPMENT or UTENSILS; (P)\n(F)     During FOOD preparation, as often as necessary to remove soil and contamination and to prevent cross contamination when changing tasks; (P)\n(G)     When switching between working with raw FOOD and working with READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\n(H)     Before donning gloves for working with FOOD; (P) and\n(I)      After engaging in other activities that contaminate the hands. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Did not wash hands","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Hands shall be washed with hot water and soap for at least 20 seconds after contamination."},{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\n\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-10-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.15","violationDescription":"(A) SINGLE-USE gloves shall be used for one task only and discarded when      damaged, soiled, or when interruptions occur in the operation. (P)\n\n(B) Slash-resistant and cloth gloves shall be used in direct contact only with FOOD that is subsequently cooked. Gloves used with ready-to-eat foods shall be smooth,   durable and non-absorbant.\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Single-use glove(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for multiple purposes","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Gloves shall only be used for one purpose and then disposed."},{"violationCode":"3-304.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall only contact surfaces of EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS that are cleaned and SANITIZED, or SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not properly cleaned and sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-10-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Equipment shall be washed, rinsed, and sanitized after contamination and between uses."},{"violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-10-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-10-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-103.11","violationDescription":"The PERSON IN CHARGE shall ensure that employees, practices and policies are in compliance with the code. (Pf) \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not ensuring compliance","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Person-in-charge must ensure compliance with items listed above."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"3-304.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cloths that are in use for wiping FOOD spills on TABLEWARE shall be maintained dry and used for no other purpose. \n(B)  Cloths in-use for wiping counters and equipment shall be held between uses in   a chemical sanitizer solution, and laundered daily.\n(C)  Cloths in-use for wiping surfaces in contact with raw animal FOODS shall be      kept separate from cloths used for other purposes.\n(D)  Dry wiping cloths and the chemical sanitizing solutions shall be free of FOOD    debris or visible soil.\n(E)  Containers of chemical sanitizing solutions shall be stored off the floor and         used in a manner that prevents contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, SINGLE-SERVICE, or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n(E)  SINGLE-USE disposable sanitizer wipes shall be used in accordance lable               instructions.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wiping cloth(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored in","subProblem":"Less than 50-100 ppm chlorine","location":"WIPING CLOTHS","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store wiping cloths in 50-100 ppm chlorine."},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not meet requirements of rule","subProblem":"","location":"FREEZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements of rule."}]},{"inspectionid":"37895","inspectionDate":"2017-02-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"DISH MACHINE","subLocation":"SANITIZING","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-02-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Equipment/utensils must be sanitized after cleaning."},{"violationCode":"3-304.15","violationDescription":"(A) SINGLE-USE gloves shall be used for one task only and discarded when      damaged, soiled, or when interruptions occur in the operation. (P)\n\n(B) Slash-resistant and cloth gloves shall be used in direct contact only with FOOD that is subsequently cooked. Gloves used with ready-to-eat foods shall be smooth,   durable and non-absorbant.\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Single-use glove(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for multiple purposes","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"At the Glove usage","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-02-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Gloves shall only be used for one purpose and then disposed."},{"violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not approved for use","subProblem":"","location":"SANITIZER BUCKETS","subLocation":"At the Sanitizer","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-02-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discontinue use."},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the COLD HOLDING TEMPERATURES","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-02-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"chlorine","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"SANITIZER","subLocation":"At the Test strips","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-02-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-501.14","violationDescription":"(A) Intake and exhaust air ducts shall be cleaned and filters changed so they are not a source of contamination by dust, dirt, and other materials. \n(B) If vented to the outside, ventilation systems may not create a public health HAZARD or nuisance or unLAWful discharge.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation system","subItem":"intake air ducts","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"At the Hood filters","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"EQUIPMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/Replace"}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"449"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}